I've got to say it.
I'm getting sick to death of these people
on social media
watching reels going, "Hook,
appeal to authority,
good product placement." Shut up, mate.
You think that's helping people with their
content?
This is how you help people with their
content and their social media.
You go through their stuff,
and you rip them a new asshole.
Now, if you would like a new asshole,
that's what I'm going to do,
and I'm going to
do it for free,
and I usually charge a fucking fortune for
this.
So there's two ways you can pay me back.
One is the link in the description where
you can give me your Instagram so I can go
have a look and give you some constructive
feedback.
Two is,
if you never want me to rip you a new
asshole, you just buy yourself some
Nutonix and ah. That will help you,
help me, to help you.
Let's get into it. I'll be real with you,
I always get super excited to do this,
and there's always just full of personal
trainers. Right, Coach Candy.
Sounds like a bit of a porn star name.
NGL,
means not going to lie for any of you
youngsters. All right.
Candy Bryant, online coach.
"Helping busy women feel confident,
strong, and at
home in their bodies again without giving
up real life." Okay,
I don't mind that. I
would probably like it to just be a little
bit shorter.
I feel that sometimes you can give people
too much in that.
Let's say me,
I help businesses make more money online
using social media.
What I don't say is,
"I help businesses between 100 and 500K
in monthly revenue make more money online
through email marketing, social
media, and creating their landing pages,
so that they can increase their
conversions whilst getting more views on
their content, whilst getting more email
addresses to send more campaigns so they
can make..." It's just too much.
Let's say you walk into a massage parlor.
You're like, "Oh, what types of massage
is it?" "Oh, we specialize in Thai massage
to help people with muscle relaxation
and de-stress." Cool.
Two things, two benefits, I believe you.
But if that massage parlor
was to say to me, "Oh, we align your inner
chakras to help your muscles relax,
and we also do spinal realignment
whilst at the same time having music
that changes your energy, mood,
and ambient
light," it's just a bit too much.
Two benefits is enough.
Anything more than that,
it's just getting a bit
much.
Helping busy women feel confident
and strong.
I think that could be better. Less
is sometimes more, just like penis
size. Having an average size cock
is the meta, I'm telling you.
Because I had a mate at uni,
not going to name him, Alex Waters,
and his cock was
way too big.
And every man growing up wants a big cock,
but he
had to break up with one girl because his
cock was too big. So where were we?
Coach Candy.
I actually quite like the branding.
All right?
Even though your name's Candy Bryant,
I like coach.candy. I'll take it.
189 posts. You are new to this,
but let's get into it. Right.
I'm seeing a lot of the old rig here in
the pinned comments.
I could be wrong,
but my first impressions,
I just hope this isn't too much about
you, but let's get into it.
"The ratio effect. Candy
is bloody incredible.
Completely different person in kind of 12
weeks." Okay, so you've been coached by
the looks of it. Why this is pinned,
I don't know.
"31 weeks,
hashtags don't do anything." The pinned
postings, right, I don't think
the pinned posts are that important,
and if they were, I'd probably use it to
showcase what you can do as a coach,
not what you've done with your body.
Because the reality is,
any person can get shredded
for their business.
Let's say I'm going to run a fat loss
challenge.
I could just get a shitload of Mounjaro
or retatrutide and then just say it
was my app. Or again, no, people starve
themselves when they're financially
incentivized.
Here's an example for you in real time.
People diet to abhorrently lean body fat
percentages for
their insurance policies.
So we all know people that
are a little bit
overweight, and you say to them,
"Do you want to lose weight?" "Nah."
Because
there's no financial incentivization.
But for a life insurance policy,
where it's going to cost you less
and pay out more
if you're at a certain body fat
percentage,
they don't eat for three weeks.
So people can refrain from doing things
with the premise and
basis that there is financial gain coming
the other side.
To get to my point,
if you get in shape as a PT,
no one believes you because they
know there is direct financial
incentivization.
Just saying that, just saying it out loud.
If you're training during Ramadan
and still trying to hit new gains,
[fart] during
Rama-
That music, that noise is so loud. I'm not
sure if I've got sensitive ears to this,
but-
Muslims fast from sunrise to sunset,
and that means no food or water during-
Right. Chat about Ramadan, great.
I think good.
But for me,
maybe it's just my generation being a
millennial,
your music,
better off being too quiet than being too
loud.
Please, too quiet than too loud. To me,
that's just overpowering, and it makes it
hard for me to listen
... hours. So straight away, energy,
hydration, and recovery are different.
It isn't the month to be chasing fat-
Because this is so great,
apart from the fact you've ruined it with
the music being
too loud. And the thing is,
people just aren't going to say to you,
"Your music's
too loud." They just won't. So please,
when we do these, just ask yourself,
"Is the
music really benefiting this?" If not,
get rid.
But always about personal bests.
I liked your B-roll, by the way,
and I like your candid piece to camera
here, which
is what it's called,
where you look at the camera and talk.
I like the backdrop.
We're outside.
We've got some natural light.
We've got more natural light on one side,
and inside probably got
the glow of some indoor lights, which
is giving you quite a warm effect.
Lighting one side of the face
is called Rembrandt. It's quite nice.
It's actually what I'm doing right now.
So if you look at my lighting here,
we have the majority of my face on the
right
side lit. If we were to bring
that more round, what I can do is I
can turn my face.
We then create more of a shadow on this
side.
So that's called Rembrandt.
When you're dramaticizing a shot,
you might turn that
light more. However,
you'll notice a bit of a shine on the side
of my face and
maybe even my delts here. See
that massive delt, right, to the outside
of that?
That's because I'm using a hair light to
the side.
So out of shot, there is a light here.
So I'm going for my A light here,
similar to what you're recreating with
your
natural light.
Then you're using a warmer fill light from
the other side.
That's why I've got a tiny bit of shadow
here.
So you've done that maybe without even
realizing, which is quite nice.
Day 43 of photo shoot prep, and
if you're wondering-
I don't like these day 43, day 42,
because if you're
my client, Miss Candy,
I want you to be growing exponentially.
You give me 126 days,
I'm going to have you a different fucking
person on social media.
And the amount of people
that will see you in the third and
fourth month They'll just feel like
they've missed season one and two.
So let's say you sit down with your
boyfriend or girlfriend,
it's 2026, and he's like,
"Let's watch 'Breaking Bad.'" You go,
"I haven't seen it.
Always wanted to watch it." He goes,
"Cool.
I'll watch the first season without you.
Let's start on season two." You'd be like,
"No way, Jose.
Not happening." So when I get here,
and you're at day 43, I'm like, "I've
missed the first 40 days.
There's no point in me even listening.
I'm off." It's like
that meme online where the guy's like,
"Imagine being born in
2025. You missed everything, bruv.
You missed everything." So yeah.
Good engagement, though. Give you that.
Come join me for my Sunday meal prep.
So I'm starting off with-
Music's too loud.
Whatever the percentage is, half it
... my lunches for-
I know you're saying, "Oh,
it's got 117 likes though." Well,
imagine what it could
have if you'd got your music in the right
place. That's what I'm saying.
[upbeat music] I've been single for almost
a year, and I
have learnt so much.
I feel like I know a lot quicker now what
I want.
Music a little bit quieter.
Really like the hook, to be honest.
Because it's a personal brand, this,
right?
So we've got your stuff where you're
helping people,
which I want to get into in a
second, but it is quite nice as well
that we see the personal,
vulnerable side of
it as well.
I don't second guess my intuition the way
that I used to, and if something-
Because this B-roll
and the footage between, and the captions,
everything, this is
fantastically done.
Albeit the music being too loud,
I'm a big fan of it.
Rushed or too intense too early on,
I notice it,
and I don't ignore it anymore.
I've learnt that slow feels better for me,
calm feels healthier, and consistency
means more than big gestures or big words.
I've also learnt how much I value my
friendships, the peop-
What's good here is you're reading a
script and covering it with B-roll. Great.
Absolutely love that.
I lost 5kg in six weeks eating Kinder
Bueno for breakfast every single day.
I am currently on a-
That music's got to stop. Okay,
what I would love,
and I'm going to say this as I
go through the next one,
in the first five seconds,
or I'll give you 10 seconds, in
the first five to 10 seconds,
I want to know exactly what problem you're
solving
for me.
There's no way in hell I would be the
person I am today without going-
Sorry, don't care. It's got me hot.
Two, three, four, five. Oh, your workout.
Sorry, don't care.
Sunday candy is the reason weekday candy
is possible.
It's day 35 of photoshoot-
Sorry, don't care. You know what I think?
I think you should stop taking directions
from people who have never- Sorry,
don't care. You're getting good likes,
by the way. You're getting good likes.
This means you got great potential.
The reason I'm roasting you
is because there is so much you can do
with this.
You have the foundational skills here.
Very good.
We just need to make the most of it by
using this.
I went to a rave sober tonight,
and I had the best time.
Guys, honest-
So again, you went to a sober rave.
That's great. Love that.
But if you were to just flip this to say,
"If you're someone that's considered
going to a sober rave,
let me tell you about this night." Because
the reason you posted this
is because you think other people care
about the
sober rave,
and I would say you're probably right in
thinking that they do.
But to tell the story,
and considering that most people on social
media don't
follow you,
if you'd only created the beginning of
this to be about you, or
about other people,
they would be more inclined to listen.
Again, I didn't start this video going,
"I'm fucking rich.
I'm a millionaire.
I've done everything you want.
I'm going to give you advice." No,
I started this video going, "If you want
feedback from me to help your business so
you can grow and you can do better on
social media, then stick along."
And I actually said, "If you need help,
you can
give me your email address,
and I will do this for you for free." This
video is
about you, not me.
So why should your video be about you
and not me? Okay.
So that's enough of el roastage.
But yeah,
love seeing a ranga getting at it. Is
that what they call it? Rangas?
Ranga. Australian. Yeah.
Ranga is a common Australian slang term
for a person with red hair. Okay.
"DM me strong for more info." Hmm.
How about I do DM
you the word strong? Not even a chatbot,
no? Not even a chatbot.
"Looks like you are going to be in my
next YouTube video. Ha ha." So why is
that not
sent? Right, so issue with that
is you could've had an automation saying,
"Just
away from my computer at the moment.
Really keen to get in touch.
Please respond with your email address,
and I'll send you everything." Now, the
other issue is here. Let's say I do,
"I am a busy woman that wants to feel
confident and strong,
and I want to feel at home in my body
again," which I don't
really know what that means. Like, oh,
go away. Feel at home in their body.
Who feels away in their body?
Who feels in their neighbor's home in
their body?
I don't really get that.
And giving up real life.
What's the alternative to giving up real
life? Giving up unreal life?
Anyway, so let's say I land on your page,
and I go, "This ranga is
killing it. This ranga
is a bloody boss babe,
and I want to work with her."
I ain't even got a website, right?
I'm ready to pay. I'm ready to buy.
I'm RTB. I'm ready to go,
and there's nowhere for me
to go. You know what I mean?
I could be here, literally wallet out,
ready
to double tap that,
and there's nothing for me here.
So we should have a website,
we should have a landing page.
We have somewhere for me to go because
right now, I could've watched all 123 days
of your prep, shoot, whatever, whatnot,
and I don't know
what you sell, how much it is,
why I need it, what I get,
or where I can pay.
And for that reason, I'm out. Okay.
Another online coach. Fantastic.
Eight posts.
Sorry, mate. No.
You need a better lip picture as well.
That's beyond Rembrandt.
You're so far past the line, the line is a
dot to you. Look at that.
Can't even see your face, mate.
If you're only going to post eight fucking
times, I'm not even going to bother,
mate. Next. Okay.
30,000 followers. Alan Parsonane.
"I hope you reconnect with your body
and mind.
Documenting the lifestyle
that changed my 20s." Okay.
Not mad on that little dot there.
That starts March, okay. We'll open that.
Join the reset. I'll have a little look.
Let's see what you do, Alan Parson.
"Build better habits with discipline with
a simple 30-day reset." All right.
I'm telling you now, I like it. Clean.
This font, beautiful.
That picture.
Uniform with the profile pic,
you're looking happy.
I like the top-down shot.
You got some little gradient on that,
maybe a little
CPR or something. Looks nice. So what
is this 30-day reset?
Join the reset.
Beautiful call to action button there.
Loving that.
Starts 1st of March, limited spots. Great.
Perfect amount of scarcity.
Not trying to be too beggy. What
is this really?
That I like, brother. What is this?
Would've worked, but what is this really?
What is this really?
I feel like it's conversational.
Let me tell you what this video
is about really.
Awareness, action, alignment. Okay.
Is this for me?
Probably not,
but I'm respecting the set right now.
What to expect after 30 days?
Mental, physical, identity. The goal
is in perfectionist alignment. All right.
The word alignment to me seems a bit
woo-hoo, but I'm there. How we get there?
Daily structure, community,
60-minute call, principles.
I'm not even reading the text.
I'm just looking what's in bold,
and I like it.
Ready to reset. Do you know what? That
is one of the nicest landing
pages I've seen in a while. Fully booked.
You just missed this one.
Oh, you dog. You fucking dog.
I reckon it was fully booked
anyway. The February reset filled up fast,
but don't worry, the next cohort is
around the corner.
I reckon someone's read a little bit of
Daniel Priestley.
Oversubscribed, and I like it.
I respect it. Next cohort March 1st.
Someone has never felt so compelled to
give an email in their life.
I tell you what, mate. I tell you what,
I see you know Kung Fu.
I like it. All right,
let's see your content.
You've obviously deleted a load of posts,
which is a bit...
You're trying to give off
that illusion like, "Oh, I'm Alan,
and I've got
30,000 followers from 68 posts." Whatever,
bruv.
What I eat in a day as a chef working in
the Swiss Alps. Hmm.
All right
Wedgie.
[upbeat music] This one slaps.
Do you know why?
It's just a nice aspirational wake up
isn't it?
"Day in the life, Swiss Alps,
building a health
and fitness community." All right.
Let's get rid of these hashtags, brother,
they don't do anything.
"Things I'll never do again." Do you know
what? I like it. Visual hook.
I don't usually like these non-piece
cameras, but I give it a
[mimics] . Looks like a bit of blackface,
but I'm not going to say anything.
I like this. It's nice. Feels nice.
I will say this though.
I could be wrong, this
is the perfect type of reel to get you
loads of
engagement, to get you loads of comments.
But just be wary of the subprime audience.
I've been there myself, brother.
Sometimes you get audience captured,
and I would ask you, honestly, did
you make this to get clients
or to get a video to go
fucking viral as fuck?
Because the two do not often go hand in
hand.
And the land is dark,
and the moon,
it-
Oh, this is kind of nice
Just to tell you that what you start
is not your final thing.
I start-
Not sure if I like the face mask, but-
Content a year ago about really like fe--
How to build better
habits.
First thing, under--
Is finding meanings harder in our modern
life?
Hey, hey, hey,
neighbor
This looks good. Good looking guy,
over six foot, living in the fucking
Swiss Alps, knows how to make content.
Bro, this is a fucking
recipe for the je ne sais quoi,
seeing as you're French, which it
turns out means,
"I don't know." I always thought je ne
sais quoi meant there is
something magical. There
is something je ne sais quoi about Jessica
Alba. All right. She's a linger,
isn't she? Anyway, so this is great.
Now, from what I see, things look amazing.
My only criticism would be I'd love to dig
a bit deeper with this, which we
obviously can't do.
I'd love to know how many
is on your email list, how
much money you're making a month.
Because those two things would determine
whether
or not you are all fart, no poo,
or you are running
a fucking fantastic business, which
is about to blow up and could scale.
And those are very different things.
So again, my strategy is the four S's.
We've got the old social, squeeze, sell,
scale.
I think that the top level, your socials,
and from what I see for your lead magnet,
look phenomenal. So your first two S's
are great.
But some people's funnels can be wide at
the top, shallow at the bottom.
I'd love to know how much money you're
making, brother.
And then if not a lot,
you could be a perfect candidate to work
with me
because let's put it this way, you
and everyone else would pay me the same
amount
of money. For you,
I don't think you'd have to do
that much to unlock a lot more
revenue. But again,
I don't really know too much about that.
I'll tell you what I'll do, Alan, for you.
If you're not on my program already,
if you join,
I'll give you a fucking three or
six-month money-back guarantee because I'm
so confident that you just giving me a
few hours of your time
that I could unlock that funnel.
Because I'll be honest with you,
you've done the hard part.
The social and the squeeze
is so flipping difficult
that unlocking the money
should be easy for you.
You can take me up on that offer.
You don't have to.
But yeah, very impressed with that.
That was nice. It's put me in a good mood.
So whoever's next,
you can thank Alan because that's real
nice, mate.
Real well done. Well done. Oh,
looks like a tattoo.
I'm looking forward to this one.
Randy Connor Tattoo, 56,000 followers.
Love this. Thank God,
not more personal trainers. Okay.
Loud tattoos for fun people. That
is fucking
fantastic, mate. Fair play. Love that.
So we've got Randy Connor Tattoo,
Portland tattoo artist,
loud tattoos for fun
people. That's great. Insinuating that
if you get a loud tattoo, you're fun.
Portland,
I've heard some crazy shit about Portland.
"Send a DM to get tattooed." Lovely call
to action. Let's have a look at this.
My name is Randy Connor.
I'm a tattoo artist in Portland, Oregon.
I do tattoos that are usually super col-
Love this, because what
I like here is
you're showcasing the results, right?
And the thing about being a tattoo artist
which is pretty good is if you were an
interior designer or a bathroom decorator
or a plumber, you have to show the
before, then the after, the before,
then the after, the before,
then the after.
Because everyone knows what skin looks
like before, you could get away with just
showing afters. That's a bit scary,
brother. It's a bit fucking scary.
Who's getting these? Who's getting these?
My mom always said to me never to shave my
head or get a tattoo.
I've now done both. Do you know what?
If you're still watching at this point,
I'll show you my tattoo, but it comes with
a caveat. This is crazy, right?
Let's just put it this way.
For those of you watching,
we'll make a little bit of a promise
together.
If I've got your name tattooed on my ass,
what the statistical chance is of that?
you at least buy my Short-Form Content
Mastery, all right? It's $99.
So statistically speaking,
we're going to roll the
dice.
If I've got your name tattooed on my ass,
you buy Short-Form Content Mastery.
All right?
For those of you that can see, it says,
"Your name." Y-O-U-R N-A-M-E.
Give me your fucking money, c-
[clears throat] people. Sorry.
Hey. [laughs] Whoo.
Oh, my gosh. So good.
Is it cute?
Yeah, it's so cute.
Okay. Okay, so-
Okay, this is really cool.
I really like this. This is cool.
These tattoos are a bit scary, bro.
They're fucking scary,
I'm not going to lie.
But I'm about it.
Hey, I'm Dina. Hip hop is this. One, two,
three,
four, hit, ah,
and ah. And a hip hop ha-
Do you know what? I love it.
I absolutely love it.
"Send a DM to get tattooed." I would love
a website here where maybe we just talk
about prices, see like prices.
Maybe you charge by the hour.
And this is where I think you could
probably flex.
Let's say you charge $500 an hour. Fine,
great.
I don't even know how much you charge for
a tattoo.
Then I'd love to see a package where you
will travel to
any person anywhere in the world,
and we make it like $50,000.
Just put it there.
You've got 56 and a half thousand
followers.
I wonder how many of them out there would
just be watching your stuff and be like,
"I want this guy to tat me."
And there's a $50,000 package.
Even if no one buys it,
suddenly the idea of spending three grand
on a tattoo
doesn't seem so crazy.
That's where I would go.
I don't know much about it,
but it looks like you're absolutely
crushing with this.
This is great. And I love the way
that you're just expressing your work
and sharing
with people. You're having fun with memes.
It's good.
I'm frightened to death by the fucking
people that are getting these, but that's
just Portland by the sounds of it.
But yeah, this is really good, mate.
Well done I'm being so nice today.
It's probably because I've had several new
tonics. All right, who's next?
Ella Graces.
I don't love the
underscores after. 34 posts,
500 followers.
That's actually pretty good.
A sports, science, health,
and nutrition student,
level three in progress.
All right. Usually, I'd be like,
"You haven't posted enough,"
but because you're
young, hungry, and studying, let's do it.
Okay, first things first.
If that's showing off your booty in your
pic, please no.
Second thing is,
I'm old enough to be your dad,
so I feel a little bit weird
looking at the old Bundesliga there.
God, I'm so old now because it
was only a flash ago that I was
19 as well.
So when I see actual 19-year-olds,
I'm like, "You're a
child.
You're actually a child." That's scary.
Okay, love to see you at it, 19,
you've got the world
ahead of you. Let's see what you're doing.
[singing] I'm a stranger in you.
54,000 likes six days ago. Jesus Christ.
Let's get rid of the hashtags.
They don't do anything.
Most teenagers who go to the gym as
children have lost their passion for their
favorite sport.
Okay,
I like it that you can tap into these
viral algorithms.
What I don't like is you sitting
and posing on a gym machine.
What I don't like is
that 54,000 people double-tapped that,
but 53,500 were like, "Yeah,
I like your post,
but I'm not following you." That's
what we want to make sure we don't do,
we don't just trend hop. Imagine this.
If I said I'll give you a random million
followers tomorrow, you probably wouldn't
say yeah because it would just be a
million followers
that have nothing to do with
your business. So on the same premise,
1,000 followers who love what you
do and your brand or a million that
are just random,
we don't want the million.
We don't want the subprime audience.
One, two, ten. Wait, what number was I on?
Fuck it. Still failure.
Cool, we're getting some meme stuff here.
Cool.
Warming up has definitely changed my leg
days for the better.
I start with-
Okay, so the hook here,
"Warming up has changed my leg days for
the better." This
ain't about you, Miss Ella. This
is about them.
If you're not warming up for your leg
days, you're missing out.
days, this is how to do it.
If you're not sure what you should be
doing before you train legs, this
is what I
would recommend. There we
are taking the exact same premise,
but making it about
them. Because at the end of the day,
people don't hire you for your workouts,
they
hire you for their workouts.
Oh my goodness me.
That was hard.
Hey, guys.
Welcome to my first ever mic up session.
We're
fixing up-
Okay, so again, no offense, no one cares.
Well, they do.
No one cares about your first mic'd up
session.
What I would love, show me a goblet squat,
tell me why they're great, tell me why I
should be doing them,
tell me why you do them
... squat. So I have a 14 kg
dumbbell right here.
So we're at a point now where we're 10
seconds in, and
there's not really anything for me here.
Now, another thing we can do
Put that down for a second.
There is a lot of background noise.
You could get rid of that using AI.
There is a good website here called
Auphonic, which quite a lot of
people use.
We're not supposed to tell people about it
because...
But you drop your audio into there,
you get a paid account, whatever,
it gets rid
of all the background noise.
If you're editing in DaVinci,
you can also get rid of
it that way. The other thing is,
if the background noise is too much,
you just film
yourself doing loads of goblets,
and then afterwards you can do a
voiceover.
A voiceover could've been a better option
here. But anyway, do you know what?
This is the thing why I'm critiquing you.
You are already so much better at making
content at 19 than I was at 25
or 26. I made my first video at 26.
So even if I
critique you, I nearly said,
"Pull your pants down,"
but I'm not saying that to a
19-year-old girl.
I'm going to sit back with a pump.
Okay, I get it.
Let's not objectify yourself. Great bum.
Love to see it.
I would much rather see it in action,
lifting some weights, doing some girl boss
shit, doing some heavy lunges. Again,
it looks like you're appeasing other
fitness chicks who do the same thing.
I want more for you than to be a set of
glutes, please, Ella.
I want you to be a voice of empowerment
for women.
I want you to be the person
that people watch and go, "Wow,
that really helped
me." What I don't want you to become is
great bum.
Because flashing your ass can get you
likes, it can get you
comments,
it can get you fucking engagement,
it can get you all those things.
You are here, Ella, to get clients,
to get high-paying clients, to be the
wealthiest of all 19-year-olds in your
county, in your borough, in your
country. By the time you're 20,
I want to see you in a nice car.
I want you to have a thriving business,
to hire people, to have staff.
What I don't want is for you to have the
most double-tapped derriere in the
world. You know what I mean?
I feel like I'm your dad.
That's a wedgie bum.
I'm sorry, Ella.
You're playing the game, that's fine,
but that's a wedgie bum.
And I'll say this,
you can't be filming like this
and then complaining that men
stare across the room.
I'm trying not to make eye contact with
the fucking thing
right here, and I'm doing this for you.
You told me to come here.
You know what I mean?
[upbeat music] I would love for just there
to be some
more explanation to this.
Let's talk about the hip thrust.
My favorite exercise in the gym
is doing the hip thrust.
What people don't realize is
that the glute has four different roles.
So I'm going to talk you through hip
extension, hip abduction, posterior pelvic
tilt. Posterior pelvic tilt,
hip abduction, hip extension,
external rotation of the
femur. Still got it. Sorry. Yeah,
so that's what I want.
I want a bit more of that.
[singing] Shape. She creeping on my mind,
but I was like, "I don't-
No. Because the thing is,
I can't rip the men for doing their
shirtless selfies
and not give you a bit of a rip here.
Great bottom. Put it away.
Stop it. You know what I'm saying?
Stop it Okay, here's going to be my
reality check, Ella.
Love to see you at it.
Love to see you doing this.
The best clients you're going to get.
I never flashed my body, right?
Because my body's pretty average.
It's not average.
It's actually massively above average.
But for me,
I never wanted to lead with my physique
because the way I help people
is not my physique.
The way I help people is the knowledge.
It's the fact I can make them feel better.
It's that I can give them the information,
and it's that I can make them
self-sufficient.
That's why I'm a good coach.
I'm a good coach because
if you hire me for three months,
you never need to hire me
again.
You cannot build a brand on the premise
that you have a good ass,
and you cannot build a brand that's
sustainable and that
you can grow off this.
I need you to occasionally, sure,
appeal to
authority, flex what you've got.
But this is not the way that you
grow into a well-established,
reputable brand that pays the bills.
Because I say this from a place of love.
Where you are right now
is between OnlyFans and personal training,
and I do not
want to see you go down the OnlyFans
route.
The
flashing the body,
the getting the bum out,
that's what OnlyFans girls do to get
fucking young pussy-less dudes to go to
their page, give them 12 pound a month.
That is not what we are here for. We
are here to solve problems.
I need you to go away
and create a list of all the problems of
the people that you
PT with or that you are soon to PT with.
I need you to start looking at people
that you look up to in the industry.
And the people that you look up to in the
industry, they can have great physiques,
but that cannot be what they
are known for. It cannot be the business.
If you want to get to the top of what you
do as a coach, you will
not do it with your physique.
I'm sorry to tell you this.
You have a great physique,
but I also would never make it to the top
using my
physique. We just don't have the genetics.
We just don't.
You're pretty, you're young, all of that,
great.
But if you just pay attention to people's
problems and you create good content and
you help them,
and you do this not to get a Gymshark
fucking
contract,
you don't do this to get a MyProtein temp
set off.
You do this with the aims of really,
truly trying to help people that are
struggling in the gym.
You can make it to the top.
If you want to be the best physique in the
UK, I'd say it's very unlikely you're
going to get there. But at 19,
if you wanted to be the number one female
fitness
influencer in the UK in five years' time,
you can absolutely do that.
But you have to do it right.
You cannot do it this way. I'm sorry.
And this link shouldn't be to TikTok.
I know you're waiting to get qualified,
but you could still be getting email
addresses from people.
I should not feel slightly uncomfortable
looking at your
stuff as a 36-year-old male. 36. Fuck. 19.
I was drinking when you were born.
How crazy is that? Last one.
Online strength coaching by Luke Selway.
Don't need to have Luke Selway there
because I can see Luke Selway.
The Luke Selway. All right. I like it.
The only annoying thing about being the
Luke Selway is that if people search for
your name,
they're not going to start with a T,
they're going to start with an L.
But it could work still.
Helping lifters break plateaus, smash PRs,
become the
strongest version of themselves.
I like it. Free training programs.
Free training programs,
join the House of Strength.
Let's get rid of free training programs
or get rid of join the House of Strength.
But no one really wants a free training
program, do they?
No one woke up today going,
"Fuck me." There's two different things
here, actually.
One, I feel, is to a lead magnet, which
is the free training program,
and the other
is to your paid course. 34 members,
33 a month.
$1,000 a month, not terrible. Oof,
it's not terrible, actually.
There's a bit all over the place as far as
a website. It sounds crazy, right?
It's quite overwhelming.
There's loads here.
I'd say to you, what
is the best thing you have here?
And just center everything around it.
As a squeeze page,
there's quite a lot of information here.
I've never seen someone crush Run School,
but I could be wrong.
Imagine a space where you're not training
alone.
You have other lifters pushing towards the
same goals, and you have everything you
need to keep making progress in one space.
That's what you're going to find within
the House of Strength.
You'll get access-
Good VSL. I like that.
33 a month seems cheap. Seems very cheap.
Okay.
So yeah,
let's just create... And also,
if you can prove to me that people
are just joining
your shit straight away, cool. If not,
everything on socials I think should go to
a
lead magnet. Everything. Everything.
And then from there,
we can send people to the website because
imagine this,
sometimes you just got to send people to
the website loads of time before they buy.
That's just how it works.
[sighs] Great back, great back.
Go on, girl. Love that.
See the one before, showing off the bum,
I feel like
there's just more class-
The last year I ran it-
It's just more classy showing off the back
like [growls] .
I feel like a woman tensing up top,
for me, just, I don't know, it feels less
seedy.
Two in-person six-week strength training
camps.
Now, the programs I use for the-
This mic, yeah,
just stick it with the magnet under the
shirt.
There's something about the collar falling
away that just doesn't, I don't like it.
Fools! Just stop playing. Fools!
"Oh,
but I can't eat 1,200 calories." That's
what a toddler eats.
Julianne actually made a great point in
this comment that I didn't get to make in
my re-
If you are a grown woman having to eat
what a toddler eats to lose weight,
you need to spend some time raising your
maintenance.
I do not care-
Keep going, keep going
Unpopular opinion, but do you know what?
Guys like it.
Okay, so this footage in footage,
if you want to
respond or react to someone doing
something, like I should watch her.
I shouldn't have you cucking in the
corner, because that's what you're doing.
You're cucking. Me
and her have got a thing going on right
now because she's
talking to me, I'm listening. You
are in the cuck chair in the Hilton Hotel
in the
corner watching us do our thing.
All right?
Look, if you want to get involved,
that's fine, but she's got to lead,
you've got
to come in.
I don't want to be watching Mr.
Android over here on his cuck phone in the
corner, which you are.
Let me listen to her, then you interject.
Then her, then interject.
If you're important enough to be here,
you should be full screen.
If she's important to watch,
she should be full screen.
1,200 calorie deficit
is 1,200 calories to me.
Then you shouldn't be dieting.
If you are a grown woman having to eat
what a-
We could have started here with you
saying,
"You might have seen this woman say
this." Boom, clips her.
She says the thing, comes back. "But
is this correct?
Well, hold on,
let's listen to a tiny bit more." Goes
back to her.
So then you can make your point.
And again, one thing I hate here is why
is there so much in the caption here, bro?
If there's that much information,
why wasn't it in the reel?
Look at those titties.
Don't like the memes. Some people do.
Weirdos.
I wouldn't use this as a way to grow your
audience.
160-kilo bench press at 18 years old
is absolutely ins-
Good hook. I like it.
You're linking someone to a video
that they're just not going
to be able to click.
Could have put a chatbot in there.
Say, "If you want the video,
comment the word." Then there could always
be a
follow-up DM in there.
If you're interested in coaching, do this.
The "lifters aren't good at sumo" argument
just doesn't make any s-
The sumo deadlift is easier than a
conventional deadlift,
and I feel like most
people know this, but there's a-
Then do it then,
PR your deadlift pulling sumo.
No one on the world stage
is giving up world-
Good reel
To die.
Don't like these.
I have a deadlift video here submitted by
a follower.
On today's episode of Dumb Things
. So this is good, actually.
But one thing I would love to see you do
is as you
start a video, pose with a question
or a statement, and kill the memes for
a start.
But seeing as your face could be
semi-unrecognizable online,
there's something you guys can do.
It's a framework where you open with three
words. Three words.
Sumo deadlifts are cheating,
and that's four.
Or 1,200 calories is enough calories to
lose fat on.
Or then to make it three words, you go,
1,200 calories is a problem.
And that's four again.
Just come out with something in three
seconds that will get
someone to pause. Just,
I feel like maybe there's some work to be
done on
the people are scrolling,
and your very first point of call could
really stop them
in their tracks. I don't like
that you've got these "Venom" clips
getting you to
break through a bit. We're getting there.
What I like is you're putting out the
reps. You're getting better.
Your views are going up.
Definitely going up.
The last year, I ran two in-person s-
See like one, two, three.
I don't really understand what's going on
here, and I'm
not reading your caption.
Don't like the memes.
"Oh, but I can't eat 1,200 calories.
That's what a toddler eats." Julianne
actually made a great point in this
comment
that I didn't get to make in my original
video, and that's 1,200 calories is
average or maybe a bit above average for a
toddler.
But if you're a five-foot-tall female,
you are below average height and
size for a female. So why
are you comparing yourself as a
below-average-size person to an average
or above average size toddler?
There could've just been a better hook
there because even I'm listening now, and
I'm not sure if I want to listen to the
rest of it.
If you are a grown woman having-
Keep going. Keep going. See,
I'm listening here.
I don't really know what's going on.
This, if it's that important,
just tell me.
Don't have me watch a deadlift
while it's there.
Unpopular opinion, but you-
Yeah.
DM me form check for your free form check
this February.
And do you know what?
I want to see more footage of you actually
critiquing
people's form then.
You know how now I'm critiquing content,
maybe we show people
that. Got some work to do,
but it goes all right.
All right, guys, remember,
if you want me to go through your stuff,
don't be a
fucking pussy,
click the link in the description.
There's also going to be things
that you can buy from me in there.
And considering that I did have your name
on my ass, it's only fair that you
probably do buy my short-form content
mastery. All right.
That's probably the nicest I've ever been
in one.
So if you like that,
you'll love all my other videos,
but YouTube recommends that
you'll like this one the most.
So check it out. Bye-bye.